A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
The path of the warrior or the path of the demon.
Think hard, Blackstar.
You still have a chance to choose the right path.
Shut up, samurai.
You don't know what you're talking about.
You've chosen the demon.
I can do nothing more for you.
Blackstar!
Where am I?
Let's go!
Blackstar!
Let go!
What am I seeing?
I'm falling down to my shadow
I'm falling down to my breath
I'm waiting for you to be waiting for you
Don't scare me
If you're looking for me
I'm falling down to my eyes
See you in your dreams, yeah, baby
Even if you're looking for me
I'm falling down to my heart
When you're lost, you are young
Forever with your soul
You can't see it, you can't see it
Hey, Free, can you hear me?
Yeah, loud and clear
Our line to Medusa has been cut off for a while
I think that might mean...
She's dead, right?
Probably so
What do you think, Mizune?
Right, which means...
Yeah, time to bail out
Is something wrong, Ox?
Uh, no
Then let's keep moving
Alright
The Miraculous Coffee Table Flip
Fly, our Death City robot
Baru
Unlock
It begins
What's it doing?
It's getting bigger and bigger
Look closely, everyone
This is Avon's ultimate creation
The magic tool Brew is assuming its true form
Lord Death
The tool is ready
Thank you, Avon
Dad, what exactly is Brew's power?
What does it do?
Brew is a unique device
Its power lies in its ability to take whatever form its wielder most desires
How is that possible?
It becomes tuned to the wielder's soul
Brew measures the strength of that soul's desire
And alters itself accordingly
And therein lies its most fearsome power
If used the wrong way, Brew could destroy the entire world
Brew's power terrified even its creator
To protect it from falling into the wrong hands
He locked the device and bound his own soul to the key
Which means the key to the magic tool is Avon's soul itself
Without the presence of its creator
Brew's power can never be activated
Lord Death
As you predicted, my research led to nothing but grief and sorrow in the end
The death of friendship
Betrayal
Involvement with witches
And the loss of the one I loved most
But now at least
I can make amends for my misdeeds by helping you
Do you remember what you said to me all those years ago?
Even if you triumph over death
You'll find nothing but grief and sorrow
For the first time
I understand what you meant
A-bomb
Save the world
Fool
Lord Death
Do you copy?
No
We have a situation
The enemy has a new weapon
At this rate
We can't hold on much longer
Looks like we're gonna need to speed things up a bit
I never seem to know what to say in situations like this
But you just said something, didn't you?
That's true, I did
Okay, I'll shut up
Yeah, so will I
The tool takes the form of its wielder's desire
What will it become for my father?
All right
Let's get this party started, shall we?
What's happening?
Dad?
Death City is moving
So you showed up again
Why are you here?
Well?
What are you trying to get back into my good graces?
I'm here to bid you farewell
What?
Don't you understand?
Understand what?
That you finally lost
Oh, yeah
Even now, you are surrounded by warriors who have lost the will to survive
Soon they'll devour you
You are deep inside the enchanted sword
This is the final destination for those whose souls have been irrevocably shattered by fear
What I saw
Those images from earlier
Farewell, weakling
We shall not meet again
You brag that you would surpass God
Instead, look where you've ended up
Hold it
We are done
Black Star
You're lost in a world of darkness
Soon it will swallow your soul and you'll be gone forever
All I can hope for you is a peaceful end
I suppose you're not lost after all
You chose the path of the warrior
Path of the warrior?
What's this?
You will never see my tears
You get it?
These tears belong to those fallen soldiers
I'll save them from their fear and sorrow
I will take up their burdens
Foolish boy
I told you you've already lost
Despair is all that remains for you
And you can never change that
That's where you're wrong
I haven't lost anything
I don't run from fear
I stand and face it
The day I lose will be the day I die
I won't be devoured and I won't give up
You will never defeat me
You're going to fight for the fallen warriors
Those left behind on the path
Nakatsukasa
I'm gonna show you a new world
Like none you've ever seen
My family's souls
We're all with you now
Mufune
Let's get something straight
The path I choose isn't that of the warrior or the demon
You don't know this path
You've never seen it before, Samurai
My path
And nobody else's
You've got me
You reject warrior and demon
And choose a path of your own making
Let's see it
Show me this path
I can't help you this path
Saw me this path
So, what if you tell me this path
Dear me, this path
Now I want to perto
I want to be on the path
You can't help me
Find me this path
Save me questions
Like outer
For me
yourself
You can助 me this way
Sorry, that way
Who wanna go
Mifune.
Go on, then. One stroke will finish me.
You're giving up, Samurai? Already?
Isn't there somebody you're still sworn to protect?
And don't forget, Tsubaki made you a pretty good offer the last time we met.
You care about helping children and you have incredible skill.
You'd fit in well at the Academy.
Why not become a teacher instead?
What? A teacher at the Academy?
You coming?
Don't worry. We'll find that little witch of yours first.
Mosquito's putting up a better fight than I expected.
That's interesting. I would have thought you'd be a bit upset.
What? Why?
Come now. Surely you've noticed what's been happening.
Spit it out already! What are you talking about?
They've been attacking indiscriminately.
In other words, arachnophobia doesn't care if you die.
What the hell? Seriously?
Seriously.
Damn that witch.
There's no hope for you now.
Lady Arachne planned well.
We just sacrificed some of our own forces.
And in doing so, we ensure that victory will be ours.
Next target sighted!
This is it.
This is where we die.
Fire!
What the...
What is that?
What the heck is that?
We made it.
But just barely.
What is that?
This was Dad's wish.
All those years ago, he bound his soul to Death City in order to seal the Kishin away.
That binding kept him trapped in the city.
There was nothing he desired more than this.
To come here to this battlefield.
And Brew made that possible by mobilizing all of Death City.
All right then.
Let's see what this baby can do.
Mosquito, launch a counter-attack.
Understood, my lady.
Launching counter-attack!
That one can move too?
Boots.
What?
This is insanity.
This can't be happening.
This is so cool!
Let's dance.
Well, here goes nothing.
What?
Why can't I swap that damn mug?
Careful, Dad! Don't kill us!
Take this mug!
Help me!
Nice try, Reaper!
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
Hot, hot! Really, really hot!
Dad, what are you doing?
I'm Hulk!
Special attack?
Coffee table flip!
Impossible!
Oops!
Now it's my team.
So this is what a Death Scythe can do?
That's incredible!
Target located. Mapping it now.
The upper level of the castle, near the middle.
That's where the Kishin is.
Thank you, Azusa. Good job.
Same to you, students. You performed well today.
Hold on tightly!
It's not over yet!
Die, Reaper!
Time's over!
They're die!
What now?
No!
He swallowed the quiesin whole!
This shrap.
Half a prelimin'
Ito-tsu-ku-tai-you-ni
Sala-sa-lete
A-pure-lu-na-mata-ga
Shita-ta-lu-mato-shisa-de
Boku-a-na-zo-u-kara
Tari-na-i-ka-sho-ta-da-um-de-a-u-yo-ni-ki-mi-yo-mo-to-mete-i-ta
触れ合う指に伝わらせつなさだけを
かき集めて
鼓動力にかざす願いを
その目というまま
残された記憶と
I've lost my face, but now I'm going to leave
Mama!
But the Kishin's all eaten. What else is left to do?
Well, it's a bit... complicated.
So it's not over?
On the next episode of Soul Eater, Lord Death wields a death scythe.
Just one step from utter darkness?
Oh goody, there's still more to come!